

CHASSANI HAEZAH

ADMINISTRASION

PROFILE

I am Chassani, I'm 27 years old. I've been working as Administrasion on my experience.

I have familiar in operating computer program such as Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, and Power Point). I am a hard worker, I have good organizational and interpersonal skill, I am fun and outgoing person, and self motivated.

CONTACT

+62 812 11039130 chaezah4@gmail.com @chassanih

BIRTH

Jakarta, 04 July 1994

ADDRESS

Jl. Baladewa Kiri No.21 RT.015 RW.003 KEL.Tanah Tinggi Kec. Johar Baru , Jakarta Pusat

LANGUAGE

Bahasa

INTEREST

Movies, Music

PERSONAL COMPETENCE

- Cooperate with team
- · Excellent service
- Public Relation
- Responsible
- On time
- Problem solving
- Fast learner
- · Strong willingness to learn new things

EXPERIENCE

July 2013 - Dec 2013

PT. Gramedia Distributor MT. Haryono, Jakarta

Sales Promotion Girl

Jan 2014 - April 2014

PT. Tri Anugrah Fashion

Senen, Jakarta

Sales Promotion Girl.

May 2014 - May 2019 KSP Srihadi Makmur

Ruko Jatibening, Bekasi

Teller, Credit Support and Staff Administrasi

Sept 2019 - Sept 2020 Oria Hotel Sarinah, Jakarta Sales Admin

EDUCATION

2010 - 2013

SMAN 22 Senior High School Utan Kayu, Jakarta

Majoring in Social Science.